[
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Bye' and 'good morning' to portuguese",
    "choice1": "Amigo, tchau",
    "choice2": "Oi, menino",
    "choice3": "Tchau, Bom dia",
    "choice4": "Oi, Tchau",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank! ____ e uma menina. (A boy and a girl)",
    "choice1": "Um menino",
    "choice2": "Uma menino",
    "choice3": "Dois meninos",
    "choice4": "Um gato",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Eu tenho um...' to english",
    "choice1": "I have a...",
    "choice2": "She has a",
    "choice3": "They have a...",
    "choice4": "Why is she....",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank! O menino ____ . (The boy eats apples)",
    "choice1": "bebe leite",
    "choice2": "como pão",
    "choice3": "come maçãs",
    "choice4": "come laranjas",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Ela tem um...' to english",
    "choice1": "She has a...",
    "choice2": "She has them...",
    "choice3": "He has them...",
    "choice4": "He is one....",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Bye' and 'good morning' to portuguese",
    "choice1": "Amigo, tchau",
    "choice2": "Oi, menino",
    "choice3": "Tchau, Bom dia",
    "choice4": "Oi, Tchau",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank! ____ e uma menina. (A boy and a girl)",
    "choice1": "Um menino",
    "choice2": "Uma menino",
    "choice3": "Dois meninos",
    "choice4": "Um gato",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Eu tenho um...' to english",
    "choice1": "I have a...",
    "choice2": "She has a",
    "choice3": "They have a...",
    "choice4": "Why is she....",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank! O menino ____ . (The boy eats apples)",
    "choice1": "bebe leite",
    "choice2": "como pão",
    "choice3": "come maçãs",
    "choice4": "come laranjas",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Translate 'Ela tem um...' to english",
    "choice1": "She has a...",
    "choice2": "She has them...",
    "choice3": "He has them...",
    "choice4": "He is one....",
    "answer": 1
  }
]
